//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"Which three sides have won the UEFA Euro on their home soil?",
        answer: "Spain,Italy,France",
        options:[
            "Sapin,Italy,portugal",
            "Spain,France,England",
            "France,Italy,Potugal",
            "Spain,Italy,France"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Who was voted as the player of the tornament in the 2008 Euro's?",
        answer: "Xavi Hernandez",
        options:[
            "Michel Platini",
            "Xavi Hernandez",
            "Frank Lampard",
            "Fernando Torres"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"Which player scored the only goal in the Euro 2004 final between Portugal and Greece?",
        answer: "Angelos Charisteas",
        options:[
            "Angelos Charisteas",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Teodoros Zagorakis",
            "Luis Figo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"When was the first European Championship held?",
        answer: "1960",
        options:[
            "1948",
            "1971",
            "1977",
            "1960"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"At which stage of Euro 2020 did England concede their first goal?",
        answer: "Semi-finals",
        options:[
            "Group Stage",
            "Round of 16",
            "Final",
            "Semi-finals"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"Who is the highest goal scorer in the Euro's History?",
        answer: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        options:[
            "Michel Platini",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Antoine Griezmann",
            "Tierry Henry"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Which team won the first ever European Championship?",
        answer: "Soviet Union",
        options:[
            "Soviet Union",
            "Hungary",
            "France",
            "Yugoslavia"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Which country was Euro 1996 played?",
        answer: "England",
        options:[
            "Spain",
            "Italy",
            "Croatia",
            "England"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"How many countries are eligible to take part in the current format of the Euro's?",
        answer: "24",
        options:[
            "32",
            "16",
            "24",
            "28"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Which goalkeeper has most clean sheet in the Euro's history?",
        answer: "Iker Casillas",
        options:[
            "Iker Casillas",
            "Gianluigi Buffon",
            "Edwin van der Sar",
            "Rui Patricio"
        ]
    },
];